<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CyberQuacker Rambling</title>
    <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CyberQuacker Rambling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One Malware to rule them all</title>
      <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/onemalwaretorulethemall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/onemalwaretorulethemall/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to bring to your attention a new and dangerous attack vector that is spreading malware through .ONE files. These files, also known as Microsoft OneNote files, may appear to be from a trusted source, but in reality, they can contain malwarel.
In recent months, we have seen an increase in the number of threat actor groups utilizing .ONE files as a means to spread malware. Groups such as Async, Qakbot, and Redline are known to have used this technique to target individuals and organizations alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A simple phish leads to a billion dollar company being breached</title>
      <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/a-simple-phish-leads-to-a-billion-dollar-company-being-breached/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/a-simple-phish-leads-to-a-billion-dollar-company-being-breached/</guid>
      <description>When we think of a company getting breached generally, people think of some advanced attack that took months of planning and execution. But in reality, most breaches are caused by simple mistakes. So in this post, I will be going over a breach that could likely happen in the future and how it could have been prevented.
So let us start with the basics. What is a breach? A breach is when an adversary gains access to a system and steals data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who the Quack are you?</title>
      <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/aboutme/e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 19:58:13 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/aboutme/e/</guid>
      <description>a
Publications The Art of Deception: Microsoft Phish Redirects Victims to a Catering Voice Recording
Double Trouble: Unmasking The EPOS Net Phishing Scheme That Turns Trust Against You
Technical C / Golang / Python. AWS, Azure, SQL, DyanmoDB, VMWare, Docker, K8, Terraform.
Work History Ive worked in many fields&amp;hellip; Im listing them from most recent to least recent.
Current - Threat Analyst - Cofense:
-Developed custom python scripts to reduce manual effort for APAC threat analysts, resulting in a daily time saving of 30 minutes per team member.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
