<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CyberQuacker Rambling</title>
    <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CyberQuacker Rambling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 20:13:34 +0930</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MercyV2WalkThrough</title>
      <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/MercyV2WalkThrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 20:13:34 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/MercyV2WalkThrough/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month, I attended a local sec talk. The main event was working to resolve the MercyV2 vulnhub box.
Unfortunately during the event, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do the box as mac m1s don&amp;rsquo;t support x86 virtual machines :P So I spent most of the night talking shit and helping teach some new cyber trainees steps on how to enumerate the box. No one finished the box or got close at the event that we know of so when I got home, I took it as a challenge to finish it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A simple phish leads to a billion dollar company being breached</title>
      <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/a-simple-phish-leads-to-a-billion-dollar-company-being-breached/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 19:58:13 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/a-simple-phish-leads-to-a-billion-dollar-company-being-breached/</guid>
      <description>When we think of a company getting breached, gerenerally people think of some advanced attack that took months of planning and execution. But in reality, most breaches are caused by simple mistakes. In this post I will be going over a breach that could likely happen in future and how it could have been prevented.
So lets start with the basics. What is a breach? A breach is when a hacker gains access to a system and steals data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who the Quack are you?</title>
      <link>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/WhoTheQuackAreYou/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 19:58:13 +0930</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hatedpw.github.io/CyberQuackers/posts/WhoTheQuackAreYou/</guid>
      <description>I am just a new cyber security professional who loves ducks.
Usually can be found doing CTF Challenges - Currently top 3% on Tryhackme
Cert training
Coding dumb projects
Learning low level bug hunting techniques (Im a sucker for memory corruption bugs that stuff is so cool)
Reversing Malware - althought i dont get enough time to do this lately :(
Certs Currently working on obtaining PNPT by TCMSecurity, will be finished by the end of july!</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
